

## **Summary**

Passionate and well-qualified mobile engineer with more than 3 years of experience. Working with Android and Flutter. Studying Agile, Clean Architecture, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares.

## Favorite technologies



# **Employment history**

Mobile developer at Megaleios June 2021 - August 2021

Mobile developer at Bean Softwares
March 2021 - June 2021

Mobile developer at Thalamus Digital July 2020 - June 2021

Mobile developer at MFIT Personal January 2020 - May 2020

#### Education

Computer Science at Univali February 2020 - Present

English at KNN Idiomas September 2020 - Present

# **Projects**

**Entrepreneur at Pineapple** 

**August 2021 - Present**A personal budget planner

Entrepreneur at iCut

May 2021 - Present

A barber appointment app

Voluntary coding instructor

May 2021 - August 2021
Teaching some friends how to c

Teaching some friends how to code.

**Entrepreneur at StudentPlus** 

August 2018 - April 2021

A study planner based on the Pomodoro technique.

#### **Details**

Itajaí, SC, Brazil contact@lucasbatista.me

### Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp

Website

### Skills

TDD
Refactoring
Clean Architecture
SOLID
Design Patterns
DevOps
UML

## Languages

English

Agile

#### **Hobbies**

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.